Hi, my name is Janelle from the Philippines,
and I've been working as a video editor for the past two years,
and specializing in short-form content for social media,
e-commerce, and video and AI-generated advertisements.
And I primarily edit in the Copter,
Filmora, DaVinci Role, and sometimes Adobe,
depending on what you need.
And I also use AI tools. Such as Google Evo,
Runway, Coding AI, Pageant,
Eleven Laws, and such. And I enjoy creating videos that help
us learn quickly, maintain a strong pacing,
and feel native to platforms like blog,
Instagram, Facebook, and YouTube Shorts.
Today, I'd like to show you my three projects that I'm proud of,
and I'll walk you through them. Project 1 is the advertisement that is
mainly shampoo. And the goal of this project was creating bold and
grab-attention advertisement like for people.
So I'm building the, a strong group that will interfere in three seconds
using a quick, fast, dynamic text,
hands-on text, and smooth transitions. I also highlighted the project's
key benefits throughout the video to keep the viewers engaged.
And the second one is AOKR's Men's Wear.
This is an AI-generated fashion advertisement.
Fashion content needs to look, ah,
clean and premium, and so I focused on showcasing that.
Floating with the cinematic visuals with transitions and
captions and music that match the brand.
And I kept the pacing fast enough to maintain the attention while keeping each
color and auto-screen to screen-time.
Time to step out. And project theme is a
woman hair treatment. Uhm,
this is for just refreshment. It's a 5-minute refreshment.
And I went with a softer and more clean editing style.
And it used clean product shots,
smooth motions, v-rolls, and elephant type animations.
And to build the trust while keeping the video engaging,
uhm, I used the Benefit Focus Visuals,
which is the blue one. And the pacing was balanced so you could still
absorb the message without losing the interest.
Uhm, now I'd like to walk you through my workflow.
Whenever I receive a product, I first read the creative brief and understand the
target audience. The product and mostly the main objective of the,
of the video. And after that, I study the reference ad to understand its
pacing and hook transitions. Uhm,
and also editing styles. And my goal isn't to copy it but to understand
what it makes it effective and apply that approach to the new project.
And for pre-installing and script requirement,
I use the JVT and other AI tools to create a stronger code,
uh, improve messaging, or come up with new creative ideas.
Uhm, and AI-generated visuals, I mainly use Evil,
Cling AI, Runway, and other AI videos,
AI applications I can use to create or enhance the video
codes. Uhm, if I, if I need the AI,
I use a gem to produce a realistic avatar with natural
lipsync. For voiceovers,
I use 11 rubs to create clean and natural sounding voices.
Once all the assets are ready, I do everything with it.
Into the editing application that I will use,
this is where I assemble the edits, build a strong opening group,
and define the pacing, and add captions,
transitions, sound effects, music, and color correction that are the two usual
ones. And throughout the process,
I make sure there's always something visually interesting happening on the screen to keep
the viewer engaged. And before exporting,
I watch the entire video several times to check the timing,
and check if there's any mistakes. And I
also compare the final edit with the original brief to make sure I've achieved
the intended objective before delivering it to the client.
And that's my workflow from brief to final delivery,
and I hope I enjoyed creating performance-driven content and using AI
to speed up production while maintaining quality.
Now, thank you for taking the time to watch my little video.
I appreciate the opportunity to apply,
and I look forward to hearing from you. And again,
thank you for watching my little video.
Bye-bye!